const tennisCards = [
  {
    question: "Who won the men's singles title at Wimbledon in 2008?",
    answer: "rafael nadal",
  },
  {
    question:"Who holds the record for the most Grand Slam singles titles in men's tennis history?",
    answer: "Roger Federer, with 20 titles"
  },
  {
    question:"Who was the first Japanese player to win a Grand Slam singles title in tennis history?",
    answer: "Naomi Osaka, who won the US Open in 2018"
  },
  {
    question:"Who won the women's singles title at Wimbledon in 2019?",
    answer: "Simona Halep"
  },
  {
    question:" Who was the first British man to win a Grand Slam singles title in tennis since 1936?    ",
    answer: "Andy Murray, who won the US Open in 2012"
  },
  {
    question:"Who has won the most French Open singles titles in women's tennis history?",
    answer: "Chris Evert, with 7 titles"
  },
  {
    question:"Who won the men's singles gold medal at the 2016 Olympics in Rio de Janeiro?",
    answer: "Andy Murray"
  },
  {
    question:"Who won the women's singles title at the Australian Open in 2020?",
    answer: "Sofia Kenin"
  },
  {
    question:"Who won the men's singles title at the US Open in 2019?",
    answer: "Rafael Nadal"
  },
  {
    question:"Who was the first player from South America to win a Grand Slam singles title in tennis history?",
    answer: "Gabriela Sabatini, who won the US Open in 1990."
  },
  

];

export default tennisCards;
